<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Architecture on Bohdan Stupak&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://wkalmar.github.io/tags/architecture/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Architecture on Bohdan Stupak&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://wkalmar.github.io/tags/architecture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Implementing clean architecture in Go</title>
      <link>https://wkalmar.github.io/post/go-clean-architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wkalmar.github.io/post/go-clean-architecture/</guid>
      <description>It has been written a lot about the clean architecture. Its main value is the ability to maintain free from side effects domain layer that allows us to test core business logic without leveraging heavy mocks.
This is accomplished by writing dependency-free core domain logic and external adapters (be it database storage or API layer) that rely on the domain and not vice versa.
In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll have a look at how clean architecture is implemented with a sample Go project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Property-based tests and clean architecture are perfect fit</title>
      <link>https://wkalmar.github.io/post/clean-architecture-and-property-based-fit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wkalmar.github.io/post/clean-architecture-and-property-based-fit/</guid>
      <description>It has been written a lot about the clean architecture. Its main value is the ability maintain free from side effects domain layer that allows us to test core business logic without leveraging heavy mocks.
However, when it comes to designing tests for out pure domain logic quite often we don&amp;rsquo;t tend to be so picky. Unit testing contains many traps such as overspecified software. But even when it comes to testing pure functions which may seem as a pretty straightforward process we may encounter some pitfalls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strive for short-lived synchronous communication</title>
      <link>https://wkalmar.github.io/post/make-synchronous-communication-short-lived/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wkalmar.github.io/post/make-synchronous-communication-short-lived/</guid>
      <description>When interacting with a service asynchronous communication often is a preferred way. &amp;ldquo;Enterprise integration patterns&amp;rdquo; book puts it that way (which also might be a TL;DR; for the rest of the article)
 With synchronous communication, the caller must wait for the receiver to finish processing the call before the caller can receive the result and continue. In this way, the caller can only make calls as fast as the receiver can perform them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building auth endpoint with Go and AWS Lambda</title>
      <link>https://wkalmar.github.io/post/building-auth-endpoint-with-go-and-aws-lambda/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wkalmar.github.io/post/building-auth-endpoint-with-go-and-aws-lambda/</guid>
      <description>When I was playing around with my pet-project Kyiv Station Walk I’ve noticed that manually removing test data is tedious and I need to come up with a concept of the admin page. This required some sort of authentication endpoint. Some super-lightweight service which would check login and password against as a pair of super-user credentials.
Serverless is quite useful for this simple nanoservice. This brings some cost-saving as serverless comes to me almost free due to low execution rate that I anticipate for the admin page of my low-popular service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Distributed locking with Redlock.net</title>
      <link>https://wkalmar.github.io/post/leader-election-with-redlock-net/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wkalmar.github.io/post/leader-election-with-redlock-net/</guid>
      <description>Why locking things Microservice architecture becomes widely adopted these days. One of the benefits it offers is the possibility of horizontal scaling which allows us to increase the performance of our application dramatically. However, there are situations when multiple instances of service face contention for some shared resource. In such a case one of the instances would acquire a lock over this resource claiming exclusive access to it. Let&amp;rsquo;s have a look at some possible use cases when this is helpful.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>