<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Go on Bohdan Stupak&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://wkalmar.github.io/tags/go/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Go on Bohdan Stupak&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://wkalmar.github.io/tags/go/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging lazy evaluation</title>
      <link>https://wkalmar.github.io/post/leveraging-lazy-evaluation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wkalmar.github.io/post/leveraging-lazy-evaluation/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m usually skeptical about leetcode tasks since this is not something you&amp;rsquo;ll encounter in your daily line-of-business code. But the idea behind this particular task has fascinated me. So I&amp;rsquo;ll break it down here.
I&amp;rsquo;ll provide a bit simplified version of the task so you could capture the gist of it more easily.
Write an API that generates fancy sequences using the append, addAll, and multAll operations. Implement the Fancy class: Fancy() Initializes the object with an empty sequence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building auth endpoint with Go and AWS Lambda</title>
      <link>https://wkalmar.github.io/post/building-auth-endpoint-with-go-and-aws-lambda/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wkalmar.github.io/post/building-auth-endpoint-with-go-and-aws-lambda/</guid>
      <description>When I was playing around with my pet-project Kyiv Station Walk I’ve noticed that manually removing test data is tedious and I need to come up with a concept of the admin page. This required some sort of authentication endpoint. Some super-lightweight service which would check login and password against as a pair of super-user credentials.
Serverless is quite useful for this simple nanoservice. This brings some cost-saving as serverless comes to me almost free due to low execution rate that I anticipate for the admin page of my low-popular service.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>